desoho.net 2011-10-16

# 

DeSOHO.com Privacy Policy

The personal information of the merchant ("Personal Information") provided by the online merchant will be handled in the following manner by DeSOHO.com ("Company").

1\. The Company will comply with laws and standards concerning the protection of Personal Information, and take all necessary measures to protect the Personal Information of the customer.

2\. The purposes of using the Personal Information  
The use of the Personal Information provided by the online merchant will be limited to the following circumstances.

Personal Information will be used:  
\- with respect to the service, a) for confirmation of the individual's identity, b) for billing purposes, c) for notification purposes in connection with changes of charges and service conditions, installation dates, service suspension, and contract termination, and d) for any other purpose necessary for the provisioning of the services; - with respect to the service and any other services provided by the Company, a) to conduct sales promotion of the Company's services, b) to conduct customer surveys and c) to send promotional materials or gifts etc by means including the use of the telephone, email and postal service;

\- for purposes of improving Company's services and for developing new services;  
\- to answer any questions or provide consultation as may be requested by the customer;  
\- for any other matters agreed by the customer, not listed above.

In addition to the use of the Personal Information listed above, the Company may from time to time specify other use purposes through provisioning of services and customer surveys.

3\. To manage the Personal Information properly, Company will protect the Personal Information provided by the merchant through continuous improvement efforts to:   
1) maintain internal regulations and internal control to protect the Personal Information,   
2) provide employee education, and   
3) take appropriate measures against illegal access, loss, destruction, falsification, and disclosure of Personal Information.

4\. Entrustment of Personal Information  
The Personal Information may be entrusted to Company's vendors or business partners to the extent reasonably necessary for the fulfillment of purposes listed above. 

In such case, Company will select appropriate vendor who have implemented necessary measures to protect the Personal Information, and the Company will take all appropriate and necessary actions including but not limited to entering into contractual agreement with such vendor to protect the Personal Information of the merchant.

Notwithstanding anything to the contrary stated above, the Company may provide Personal Information of the affiliates and partners to Governmental authority (e.g. Courts and Police) if required or requested properly pursuant to law. 

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Site.

5\. Helpdesk Services  
If you wish to request disclosure of your Personal Information which you have provided to us, please contact the following Helpdesk. The Helpdesk will respond to your request in a reasonably timely manner. For any inquiries regarding protection of your Personal Information please submit your request at our Service Center at CONTACT page.
